hello I am dandas and I am pursuing pgdm
in marketing operations from PBM today I
am thrilled to announce that I got
placed in ic Lumbard as a management
trading if I'm talking about my
academics I just learned a lot of things
like marketing aspects and marketing
concepts like CRM customer relationship
management direct sales personal selling
B2B sales and marketing strategy and
marketing development while I am talking
about my experience in internship I was
placed in ITC kolata in my winter
internship program where I understand
about Channel sales and channel
distribution and I was placed in AA
excellente in my summer internship
program where I understand how to
negotiate and how to build a good
relationship with customers through
these are the basic things which
actually helped me to get placed in icsi
Lumbard
[Music]